# **Anton Vice**

Data Scientist With Deep Learning Experience

### Contact

#### **Address**

Singapore, Singapore 179868

#### **Phone**

+6282146598234

#### E-mail

architect@deepvice.co

#### **WWW**

DeepVice.co

#### **www**

github.com/antonvice

## **Skills**

Agile

Excellent

Statistical analysis

Excellent

Machine learning

Excellent

Data Mining

Very Good

Machine Learning
Integration

Excellent

Project Management

Very Good

English

Excellent

A Data Scientist with experience in machine/deep learning and predictive modelling. Skilled in Python, SQL, Tableau, AutoML tools, and web and mobile application development. Experienced in working with large datasets to find trends and build models to predict outcomes. Strong communication skills with the ability to present complex data analysis in a clear and concise manner.

# **Work History**

2020-03 -2022-08

## Lead MLops

DeepVice Startup, Singapore

- Managed team of employees, overseeing hiring, training and professional growth of employees.
- Developed team communications and information for video meeting with Miro board and Trello
- Collected clients' preferences on features to be included in the UX/UI design, data streams, and machine learning models
- Created Agile software development sprints for the Design and Development teams.
- Engineered machine learning apps with Bubble, Adalo, Streamlit, and Flask: set up the design layouts; included data gathering, data preprocessing, and data analysis pipelines; developed machine learning models to be used on the data streams that resulted in 4 working MVPs and 2 final products currently utilized by restaurant and fitness businesses

2020-01 -2021-03

## **Data Scientist**

Vice City Living LLC, Miami, Florida

- Performed market analysis with scraped off the internet data with Python, defining the scope and target audience for the business
- Led a marketing team of 4 people, developing marketing and sales data streams for the optimization of the marketing strategies.
- Utilized A/B testing on social media marketing campaigns, reducing the marketing costs of the company by 50%
- Optimized the entire analytics and machine learning pipeline with Snowflake platform cutting employee costs by 75%



2018-03 -2019-12

## **Data Scientist**

JetBoat Miami, Miami, Florida

- Translated cost and benefits of machine learning technology for non-technical audiences.
- Implemented a new data processing pipeline that reduced processing time by 80% while also increasing accuracy by 10%.
- Integrated data streams with Zappier, airtable, and excel sheets
- Created data visualization graphics with Tableau and Seaborn, translating complex data sets into comprehensive visual representations.
- Assisted with creating and updating inventory and marketing strategies based on insights derived from data analysis which reduced marketing costs by 20% and inventory savings of 30%
- Utilized AutoML tools for prediction automation which reduced the time costs for predictions while maintaining high model validity of >80%

2017-01 -2018-05

# **Data Analyst**

Dolphin Family Tours, Cocoa Beach, FL

- Analyzed transactions system and PoS to develop tables from incoming data streams with SQL and Excel
- Built machine learning pipelines with scikitlearn
  which combined preprocessing of data: cleaning
  the null values, feature engineering and feature
  enrichment, encoding the categorical variables;
  feeding the preprocessed data into several
  machine learning models for categorization or
  regression; optimizing parameters with
  GridSearch; and evaluation and comparison of
  the models a to predict customer return
- Analyzed marketing strategies of local competitors to synthesize complex analyticsderived insights into easy-to-understand, actionable service recommendations for clients that were presented with Tableau

2016-09 -2017-12

# **Data Analyst Intern**

Nemo Submarines Del Caribe, Isla Mujeres

 Gathered data for analysis with webscraping tools BeautifulSoup and ParseHub

- Identified, analyzed and interpreted trends with Python's libraries Pandas, numpy, and scikitlearn to identify optimal marketing strategy which resulted in cutting marketing costs by 15%
- Created visual representations of analysis findings with matplotlib, ggplot, and seaborn to present the information to the management in concise and understandable form.
- Preprocessed data by dealing with NaN values and outliers resulting in accurate data analysis.

# **Education**

2021-01 - 2022-09	Professional Certificate: Data Science Generalist Skillfactory - Moscow, Online
2021-04 - 2021-12	Certification: Machine Learning Stanford University - Online
2017-03 - 2019-09	Bachelor of Science Florida International University - Miami, Florida
2015-08 - 2017-05	Associate of Science: Information Technology
	University of South Florida, Sarasota-Manatee - Sarasota, Florida

# Certifications

2022-08	Supervised Machine Learning @ Stanford
2022-07	UX/UI DEsign @ Google
2022-05	AR/VR/MR/XR: Technologies, Applications & IssuesIntro to AR/VR/MR/XR: Technologies, Applications & Issues

# **Interests**

Programming

Surfing

Traveling